Press Shift-X to display the X-Ray combination and adjust the model's bone.
Before adjusting, click on the icon in the upper right corner of the locator to use the symmetrical edit function.
Press again to turn off and adjust the node separately.
After selecting a node, press Shift-X to return to the normal human body surface.
References and adjustments at the same time.
If the background is a default mirror color, you may not be able to see the bone grid, so you can replace the background.
In the 3D window background, right-click and select Set 3D background.
Select the texture or color block to fill in if needed.
Then you can adjust the bone grid position as needed.
Of course, if you are adjusting the posture of the external software, you can use the Morph Target function.
Please refer to the animation production video for how to use it.
After the adjustment is complete, you can save the current pose as a posture file for later use.
This pose can be downloaded from the address in the shortcut.
This is the first time I have used the Morph Target function.
You can see that the model is now in the 3D world.
I will show you the 3D model in a moment.
In the basic model, you can see that the model is in the 3D world.
The model has three parts, and the model is in the 3D world.
This model is in the 3D world.
The model is in the 3D world, and the model is in the 3D world.